<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="twisters_hard">
        <item>Swan swam over the sea, swim, swan, swim!
            Swan swam back again well swum, swan!</item>
        <item>A sailor went to sea to see what he could see.
            And all he could see was sea, sea, sea</item>
        <item>I saw Susie sitting in a shoeshine shop.
            Where she shines, she sits, and where she sits, she shines</item>
        <item>Whether the weather is warm, whether the weather is hot, we
            have to put up with the weather, whether we like it or not</item>
        <item>If you must cross a course cross cow across a crowded cow crossing,
            cross the cross coarse cow across the crowded cow crossing carefully</item>
        <item>Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear,
            Fuzzy Wuzzy had no hair,
            Fuzzy Wuzzy wasn\'t very fuzzy, was he?</item>
        <item>Through three cheese trees three free fleas flew</item>
        <item>I suggest that you chew a few chips and a chop at Skipper
            Zipp\'s Clipper Ship Chip Chop Shop</item>
        <item>Luke Luck likes lakes. Luke\'s duck likes lakes. Luke Luck licks lakes. Luck\'s duck licks lakes</item>
        <item>Mr. Gump has a seven hump Wump. So if you like to go Bump! Bump! Just jump on the hump of a Wump of Gump</item>
        <item>A tweetle beetle noodle poodle bottled paddled muddled duddled fuddled wuddled fox in socks, sir!</item>
        <item>As he gobbled the cakes on his plate, the greedy ape said as he ate,
            The greener green grapes are, the keener keen apes are to gobble green grape cakes. They\'re GREAT!</item>
        <item>Slow feet, quick feet. Trick feet, sick feet. Up feet, down feet. Here come clown feet.
            Small feet, big feet. Here come pig feet. His feet, her feet. Fuzzy fur feet</item>
        <item>If your daddy\'s name is Dwight, and he likes to look at birds at night,
            the gift for Dwight that might be right is a Bright Dwight Bird-Flight Night-Sight Light</item>
        <item>Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers.
            A peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked.
            If Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers?
            Where\'s the peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked</item>
        <item>How much wood would a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood?
            He would chuck, he would, as much as he could, and chuck as much wood,
            as a woodchuck would if a woodchuck could chuck wood.</item>
        <item>She sells sea shells by the seashore.</item>
        <item>Betty bought a bit of butter.
            But the butter Betty bought was bitter.
            so Betty bought a better butter,
            and it was better than the butter Betty bought before.</item>
        <item>Silly Sally swiftly shooed seven silly sheep.
            The seven silly sheep Silly Sally shooed
            Shilly-shallied south.
            These sheep shouldn\'t sleep in a shack;
            Sheep should sleep in a shed.</item>
        <item>The sixth sick sheik\'s sixth sheep\'s sick</item>
        <item>Round the rough and rugged rock the ragged rascal rudely ran</item>
        <item>Amidst the mists and coldest frosts,
            With stoutest wrists and loudest boasts,
            He thrusts his fists against the posts,
            And still insists he sees the ghosts</item>
        <item>These thousand tricky tongue twisters trip thrillingly off the tongue.</item>
        <item>Three thin thinkers thinking thick thoughtful thoughts</item>
        <item>Of all the felt I ever felt,
            I never felt a piece of felt
            which felt as fine as that felt felt,
            when first I felt that felt hat\'s felt</item>
        <item>I wish to wish the wish you wish to wish,
            but if you wish the wish the witch wishes,
            I won\'t wish the wish you wish to wish</item>
        <item>I thought a thought.
            But the thought I thought wasn\'t the thought I thought I thought.
            If the thought I thought I thought had been the thought I thought, I wouldn\'t have thought so much</item>
        <item>Perspicacious Polly Perkins purchased Peter\'s product
            And peddled pickles to produce a pretty profit!</item>
        <item>Moses supposes his toeses are roses,
            but Moses supposes erroneously;
            for nobody\'s toeses are poses of roses,
            as Moses supposes his toeses to be</item>
        <item>How much wood would a woodchuck chuck
            If a woodchuck could chuck wood?
            He would chuck, he would, as much as he could,
            And chuck as much as a woodchuck would
            If a woodchuck could chuck wood</item>
        <item>If you must cross a course cross cow across a crowded cow crossing,
            cross the cross coarse cow across the crowded cow crossing carefully</item>
        <item>Brisk brave brigadiers brandished broad bright blades, blunderbusses, and bludgeons — balancing them badly</item>
        <item>Can you can a canned can into an un-canned can like a canner can can a canned can into an un-canned can?</item>
        <item>Imagine an imaginary menagerie manager managing an imaginary menagerie</item>
        <item>Rory the warrior and Roger the worrier were reared wrongly in a rural brewery.</item>
        <item>I saw a saw that could out saw any saw I ever saw saw. If you happen to see a saw
            that can out saw the saw I saw saw I’d like to see the saw you saw saw</item>
        <item>How many berries could a bare berry carry, if a bare berry could carry berries? Well, they can\'t carry berries
            (which could make you very wary) but a bare berry carried is more scary!</item>
        <item>Something in a thirty-acre thermal thicket of thorns and thistles thumped
            and thundered threatening the 3-D thoughts of Matthew the thug –
            although, theatrically, it was only the thirteen-thousand
            thistles and thorns through the underneath of his thigh that
            the thirty-year-old thug thought of that morning</item>
        <item>Luke Luck likes lakes. Luke\'s duck likes lakes. Luke Luck licks lakes. Luck\'s duck
            licks lakes. Duck takes licks in lakes Luke Luck likes. Luke Luck takes licks in lakes duck likes</item>
        <item>Mary Mac\'s mother\'s making Mary Mac marry me. My mother\'s making me marry Mary Mac.
            Will I always be so Merry when Mary\'s taking
            care of me? Will I always be so merry when I marry Mary Mac?</item>
        <item>Six sick hicks nick six slick bricks with picks and sticks</item>
        <item>Any noise annoys an oyster but a noisy noise annoys an oyster more</item>
        <item>Rory the warrior and Roger the worrier were reared wrongly in a rural brewery</item>
        <item>Fred fed Ted bread and Ted fed Fred bread</item>
        <item>The 33 thieves thought that they thrilled the throne throughout Thursday</item>
        <item>Each Easter Eddie eats eighty Easter eggs</item>
        <item>Lesser leather never weathered wetter weather better</item>
        <item>The sixth sick sheik\'s sixth sheep\'s sick</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>