<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
       <string name="linguistic_pyramids_desc">The exercise will help you understand your thinking patterns,
           develop skills of generalization, separation and transition by analogy.
           Your task is to assign the item to a higher class,
           split into a lower class or find an analogy.
           An example is a mug. The mug can be defined
           to a higher class - tableware. Thus, we switched to 1
           class upstairs (generalized the mug over the dishes). A cup of coffee,
           tea, half a liter, aluminum, porcelain
           divided into different subspecies of mugs).
           Other types of dishes, plates, bowls, etc. are analogies
    </string>

    <string name="raven_look_like_a_table_desc">Exercise will help you break your own stereotypes,
        habits of thinking in a certain way.
        There will be two words on the screen, you need to say how one is similar to another.
        For example, a hedgehog and a motorcycle. The motorcycle has spikes on its wheels
        the hedgehog also has thorns - needles, he can
        gather in a ball like a wheel. After practicing this exercise for a few days,
        you can easily explain to anyone why a mosquito and champagne represent
        are two sides of the same coin.
    </string>

    <string name="raven_look_like_a_table_filings_desc">Exercise will help break your own stereotypes,
        habits of thinking in a certain way.
        You will be given two words to complete the exercise.
        The first is an emotion or state, and the second is an object.
        Try to tell how similar they are.
        After several repetitions of this exercise, you
        can easily say what the soul and the tank have in common.
        Elementary: helicopters are the souls of dead tanks!
    </string>

    <string name="advanced_binding_desc">This exercise will help you develop the ability to create multiple
        connections between two objects.
        There will be two words on the screen. Try to find similarities
        between two seemingly unrelated objects.
        For example, how is a watch similar to a player?
        The wheel on the side of the clock is used to set the time, and in the player
        special buttons do this. If the wheel can be rotated back and forth,
        then the player has two buttons that rotate the cassette back and forth.
        The arrow on the watch helps us understand what it is showing.
        In the player, this function is a screen
    </string>

    <string name="what_i_see_i_sing_about_desc">The exercise will teach you how to build a logical sequence
        thoughts during a conversation.
        On the screen you will see the name of the item,
        Your task is to tell something on this topic as long as possible.
        Why is this important on a human scale?
        What is it used for? Its history, functions and reasons for its birth.
        You can also raise the issue of its vital necessity to maintain world peace.
        To begin with, try to describe the topic for at least 2-3 minutes,
        with experience, the bar needs to be raised higher and higher.
        With regular practice, you can soon make your way to an hour-long lecture about an eraser, a chair, or a cabinet door.
        For example, flowers. Flowers are plants that grow in the ground,
        require watering and sun. Therefore, they only grow in summer. They come in different shapes, different colors.
        My favourite flowers…
    </string>

    <string name="storyteller_improviser_desc">Exercises will help you practice the following skills: skill
        build a logical sequence
        in the story, move from thought to thought, constantly talk about something.
        You will be given 4 words to do the exercises. Using these words, try to compose a small
        (sentences 5-6) a story in which all words are included,
        were used according to some logic and, preferably,
        used in order.
        For example, a window, a phone, a snail, slippers.
        I was looking out the window, at that moment the phone rang
        running to the pipe, I almost stepped on a snail,
        it is unclear how he ended up in my house. Probably,
        climbed through the open window. It\'s good that I didn\'t step on it, otherwise I would have to rip off it from my slippers.
    </string>

    <string name="other_abbreviations_desc">Exercise will help you develop skills
        associative connections, creative thinking, integrate everything together and at once.
        The abbreviation will appear on the screen. Your task is to come up with a decoding of this abbreviation,
        as unlike as possible in meaning to the original.
        Examples: DSM - System Modulation Database. FSD - Faces
        URC - Union of Right Comrades.
    </string>

    <string name="magic_naming_desc">The exercise will help you develop an "alternative" view of things,
        the ability to discuss what is happening "from a different angle."
        Your task is to come up with as many adjectives as possible for the noun,
        and endow the word with new unexpected properties.
        Examples: orange mood, sour hat,
        monotonous plate, ringing pills,
        pale fork, crisp chair.
    </string>

    <string name="buying_selling_desc">This exercise will help you develop persuasion skills.
        It\'s kind of like a classic "sell me a pen" problem in a job interview.
        Describe the positive qualities of the subject,
        pay attention to its disadvantages in particular, prove how people need it.
        For example, a pen.
        I am ready to offer you a pen that you can always carry with you.
        It\'s not too big and will fit in any pocket. It doesn\'t leak
        so you won\'t stain your clothes. She also has a large supply of ink.
        - with active use, they are enough for six months. Moreover,
        it can be written anywhere and in any way - even on the ceiling or on a very uneven surface.
    </string>

    <string name="remember_all_desc">Exercise will help you build up your vocabulary.
        Your task is to name at least 15 words that begin with the letter that will be on the page.
        For example: abbreviation, application, applicant, aqualung, action,
        address, administration, abstraction, agent, agreement, airplane,
        airport, alarm, angle, animal
    </string>

    <string name="co_authored_with_dahl_desc">This exercise will help you develop your creative thinking skills.
        Your task is to give an extremely precise and detailed definition of the word.
        Develop your thought and do not limit yourself to one sentence, explain the meaning of the word as follows,
        so that the possibility of confusing it with another was excluded.
        For example, shocking. Shocking is an action aimed at causing
        is extremely surprised on the verge of shock, which is often accompanied by the exclamation "Waaaaah!
       </string>

    <string name="rorschach_test_desc">The exercise will help you develop your imagination and creative thinking skills.
        Your task is to come up with what else the subject given to you can be.
        For example, an ashtray is a cemetery of cigarette butts.
    </string>

    <string name="will_not_be_worse_desc">This exercise will help you develop your creative thinking skills.
        Your task is to come up with what he can say, do,
        the worst representative of a particular profession in the world.
        For example, the worst hairdresser in the world cuts hair with gasoline and a lighter.
    </string>

    <string name="question_answer_desc">The exercise will help develop ease of speech, the ability to answer any questions.
        Your task is to answer the question as fully and creatively as possible.
        Don\'t be limited to one sentence, try
        talk as long as possible.
        For example, how do you spend your free time?
        I usefully spend my time reading books.
        With the help of books, I gain knowledge and become smarter. For example, I recently read a book
        "Anatomy of the human body" and now I know how a person works.
        In my free time I also go in for sports. Sport makes me stronger and healthier…
    </string>

    <string name="nouns_desc">The exercise will help you expand your active vocabulary.
        You have one minute to name as many nouns as possible.
        You cannot repeat yourself. After the spoken word
        click anywhere on the screen to record the result.
        This exercise is great for extracting words from passive vocabulary.
        Good mark - 54 words or more.
    </string>

    <string name="adjectives_desc">The exercise will help you expand your active vocabulary.
        You have one minute to name as many as possible adjectives.
        You cannot repeat yourself. After the spoken word
        click anywhere on the screen to record the result.
        This exercise is great for pulling words out of passive vocabulary.
        Good mark - 46 words or more.
    </string>

    <string name="verbs_desc">The exercise will help you expand your active vocabulary.
        You have one minute to name as many verbs as possible.
        You cannot repeat yourself. After the spoken word
        click anywhere on the screen to record the result.
        This exercise is excellent for "pulling" words from the passive stock.
        Good mark - 42 words or more.
    </string>

    <string name="tongue_twisters_desc">Tongue twisters will improve your speech intelligibility.
        First you need to say the text slowly.
        Don\'t try to pick up speed right away. This is mistake.
        After you\'ve already learned slowly
        pronounce a tongue twister after reading all the syllables
        and letters, work on articulation.
        Say the tongue twister silently.
        After you have worked
        with a movement of your lips, pronounce the text in a voice to the floor, in a whisper.
        In this case, the pronounced sounds should be clear,
        Even though they sound quiet.
        So, you learned clearly and distinctly, quietly
        pronounce a tongue twister. It\'s time to say it out loud
        but still slow and clear. Take your time to pronounce quickly.
        Only now, when you have completed the 4 previous steps, worked through the text,
        learned a tongue twister at a slow pace, learned to pronounce it in a whisper
        and loudly you can move on to acting. Now try to pronounce
        text in different styles, with different intonation, at different speeds. Smoothly, in a melodious voice,
        quickly, with accents (accents), acceleration, deceleration, lower voice, increase, rhythmically,
        try to sing, then quickly again
    </string>

</resources>