<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="twisters_very_hard">
        <item>A tutor who tooted the flute tried to tutor two tooters to toot.
            Said the two to the tutor, “Is it harder to toot or to tutor two tooters to toot?”</item>
        <item>I thought a thought but the thought I thought, wasn\'t the thought you thought I thought.
            If the thought I thought, had been the thought I thought, I wouldn\'t have thought I thought</item>
        <item>Chester cheetah chews a chunk of cheap cheddar cheese.
            If the chunk of cheese chunked Chester cheetah,
            What would Chester cheetah chew and chunk on?</item>
        <item>She sells seashells on the seashore.
            The shells she sells are seashells, I\'m sure.
            And if she sells seashells on the seashore, then I\'m sure she sells seashore shells.</item>
        <item>If one doctor doctors another doctor, then which doctor is doctoring the doctored doctor?
            Does the doctor who doctors the doctor, doctor the doctor the way the doctor is doctoring doctors?</item>
        <item>Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers; a peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked.
            If Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers, where\'s the peck of pickled peppers that Peter Piper picked?</item>
        <item>How much wood would a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood?
            He would chuck, he would, as much as he could, and chuck as much wood
            as a woodchuck would if a woodchuck could chuck wood.</item>
        <item>How much dew does a dewdrop drop
            If dewdrops do drop dew?
            As do dewdrops drop
            If dewdrops do drop dew.</item>
        <item>Betty Botter bought a bit of butter.
            “But,” she said, “this bit of butter\'s bitter,
            But a bit of better butter mixed with this butter might just make my bit of bitter butter better.”
            So, Betty bought a bit of better butter to make her bitter butter better</item>
        <item>Yellow butter, purple jelly, red jam, black bread.
            Spread it thick, say it quick!
            Yellow butter, purple jelly, red jam, black bread.
            Spread it thicker, say it quicker!
            Yellow butter, purple jelly, red jam, black bread.
            Don\'t eat until you are spreading it like a spread!</item>
        <item>The sixth sick sheikh\'s sixth sheep\'s sick</item>
        <item>Pad kid poured curd pulled cod</item>
        <item>Pad kid poured curd pulled cod</item>
        <item>Six sick hicks nick six slick bricks with picks and sticks</item>
        <item>The sixth sheik\'s sixth sheep is sick</item>
        <item>The sixth sheik\'s sixth sheep is sick</item>
        <item>I slit the sheet, the sheet I slit, and on the slitted sheet I sit</item>
        <item>Give papa a cup of proper coffee in a copper coffee cup</item>
        <item>Denise sees the fleece, Denise sees the fleas. At least Denise could sneeze
            and feed and freeze the fleas</item>
        <item>Betty Botter bought some butter. “But," said she,
            "this butter\'s bitter! If I put it in my batter,
            it will make my batter bitter. But a bit of better
            butter will but make my batter better." Then she bought
            a bit of butter, better than the bitter butter, made
            her bitter batter better. So \'twas better Betty
            Botter bought a bit of better butter!</item>
        <item>A tutor who tooted the flute tried to teach two young
            tooters to toot. Said the two to the tutor,
            "Is it harder to toot, or to tutor two tooters to toot?"</item>
        <item>If you must cross a coarse, cross cow across a crowded
            cow crossing, cross the cross, coarse cow across the crowded cow crossing carefully</item>
        <item>Kenny the anemone met twenty enemies when he mentioned the many men he
            sees. "Again," said the enemy anemones, "again he mentions the
            many men he sees." Now Kenny the enemy anemone has twenty new frenemies</item>
        <item>Lions lie and liars lie. Lions lie limply alive and liars lie
            liberally alive. Lions likely lie liberally but liars are likely liable for liking lying and light libel</item>
        <item>Sue the sushi chef sued Sue the sous chef.
            So Sue the sous chef soon sued Sue the sushi chef. She sued so she should share her sushi</item>
        <item>Twins twist tweed twine twice. The tweed twangs and twitches as the twins twist.
            It twinkles and twists as two twins twiddle and tweeze the twirling twine</item>
        <item>Chris crosses the criss-crossed crews on the crystal cruise.
            He caresses cress crosses and crosses the crystal crews at the crux of the crossed cruise</item>
        <item>Sing a single synonym for cinnamon since cinnamon synonyms are simply singable.
            Singeing cinnamon sounds like sinning cymbals; singing synonyms sends sinewy symbols to singles</item>
        <item>All I want is a proper cup of coffee,
            Made in a proper copper coffee pot
            I may be off my dot
            But I want a cup of coffee
            From a proper coffee pot.
            Tin coffee pots and iron coffee pots
            They\'re no use to me -
            If I can\'t have a proper cup of coffee
            In a proper copper coffee pot
            I\'ll have a cup of tea</item>
        <item>What a to do to die today
            At a minute or two to two
            A thing distinctly hard to say
            And harder still to do.
            For they\'ll beat a tattoo at twenty to two
            A rat-tat-tat-Tat-tat-tat-Tat-tat-tat-too
            And the dragon will come when he hears the drum,
            At a minute or two to two today
            At a minute or two to two.</item>
        <item>Ingenious iguanas improvising an intricate impromptu on impossibly-impractical instruments.</item>
        <item>She sells seashells by the seashore.
            The shells she sells are surely seashells.
            So if she sells shells on the seashore,
            I\'m sure she sells seashore shells.</item>
        <item>Mr. See owned a saw.
            And Mr. Soar owned a seesaw.
            Now, See\'s saw sawed Soar\'s seesaw
            Before Soar saw See,
            Which made Soar sore.
            Had Soar seen See\'s saw
            Before See sawed Soar\'s seesaw,
            See\'s saw would not have sawed
            Soar\'s seesaw.
            So See\'s saw sawed Soar\'s seesaw.
            But it was sad to see Soar so sore
            just because See\'s saw sawed
            Soar\'s seesaw.</item>
        <item>A tree-toad loved a she-toad
            Who lived up in a tree.
            He was a two-toed tree-toad,
            But a three-toed toad was she.
            The two-toed tree-toad tried to win
            The three-toed she-toad\'s heart,
            For the two-toed tree-toad loved the ground
            That the three-toed tree-toad trod.
            But the two-toed tree-toad tried in vain;
            He couldn\'t please her whim.
            From her tree-toad bower,
            With her three-toed power,
            The she-toad vetoed him</item>
        <item>Ned Nott was shot and Sam Shott was not.
            So it is better to be Shott than Nott.
            Some say Nott was not shot.
            But Shott says he shot Nott.
            Either the shot Shott shot at Nott was not shot,
            Or Nott was shot.
            If the shot Shott shot shot Nott, Nott was shot.
            But if the shot Shott shot shot Shott,
            Then Shott was shot, not Nott.
            However, the shot Shott shot shot not Shott, but Nott</item>
        <item>Betty Botter had some butter,
            But, she said, "this butter's bitter.
            If I bake this bitter butter,
            It would make my batter bitter.
            But a bit of better butter,
            That would make my batter better."
            So she bought a bit of butter –
            Better than her bitter butter –
            And she baked it in her batter;
            And the batter was not bitter.
            So \'twas better Betty Botter
            Bought a bit of better butter</item>
        <item>Theophilus Thistle, the Thistle Sifter,
            Sifted a sieve of unsifted thistles.
            If Theophilus Thistle, the Thistle Sifter,
            Sifted a sieve of unsifted thistles,
            Where is the sieve of un-sifted thistles
            Theophilus Thistle, the Thistle Sifter, sifted?</item>
        <item>Esau Wood sawed wood.
            Esau Wood would saw wood with a wood saw.
            Esau\'s wood saw would saw wood!
            One day, Wood\'s wood saw would saw no wood,
            so Wood sought a wood saw that would.
            Then, Wood saw a wood saw saw wood as no
            wood saw Wood ever saw wood sawed wood.
            So Wood sought the wood saw that sawed wood
            as no wood saw Wood ever saw ever sawed.
            Now Wood saws wood with the wood saw Wood
            saw saw wood as no wood saw
            Wood ever saw would wood saw wood</item>
        <item>Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers;
            A peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked;
            If Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers,
            Where\'s the peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked</item>
        <item>How much wood would a woodchuck chuck
            if a woodchuck could chuck wood?
            He would chuck, he would, as much as he could,
            and chuck as much wood as a woodchuck would
            if a woodchuck could chuck wood.</item>
        <item>Betty Botter bought some butter but, said she, the butter\'s bitter.
            If I put it in my batter, it will make my batter bitter.
            But a bit of better butter will make my bitter batter better.
            So she bought some better butter, better than the bitter butter,
            put it in her bitter batter, made her bitter batter better.
            So \'t was better Betty Botter bought some better butter</item>
        <item>She sells seashells on the seashore.
            The shells she sells are seashells, I\'m sure.
            And if she sells seashells on the seashore,
            Then I\'m sure she sells seashore shells</item>
        <item>Birdie birdie in the sky laid a turdie in my eye.
            If cows could fly I\'d have a cow pie in my eye</item>
        <item>How much ground would a groundhog hog, if a groundhog could hog ground?
            A groundhog would hog all the ground he could hog, if a groundhog could hog ground</item>
        <item>Yellow butter, purple jelly, red jam, black bread.
            Spread it thick, say it quick!
            Yellow butter, purple jelly, red jam, black bread.
            Spread it thicker, say it quicker!
            Yellow butter, purple jelly, red jam, black bread.
            Don\'t eat with your mouth full!</item>
        <item>I thought a thought.
            But the thought I thought
            Wasn\'t the thought I thought I thought.
            If the thought I thought I thought,
            Had been the thought I thought,
            I wouldn\'t have thought I thought</item>
        <item>Something in a thirty-acre thermal thicket of
            thorns and thistles thumped and thundered threatening
            the three-D thoughts of Matthew the thug – although,
            theatrically, it was only the thirteen-thousand thistles
            and thorns through the underneath of his thigh that the
            thirty-year-old thug thought of that morning</item>
        <item>To sit in solemn silence in a dull, dark dock,
            In a pestilential prison, with a life-long lock,
            Awaiting the sensation of a short, sharp shock,
            From a cheap and chippy chopper on a big black block!
            To sit in solemn silence in a dull, dark dock,
            In a pestilential prison, with a life-long lock,
            Awaiting the sensation of a short, sharp shock,
            From a cheap and chippy chopper on a big black block!
            A dull, dark dock, a life-long lock,
            A short, sharp shock, a big black block!
            To sit in solemn silence in a pestilential prison,
            And awaiting the sensation
            From a cheap and chippy chopper on a big black block!</item>
        <item>Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers
            A peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked
            If Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers
            Where\'s the peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked?</item>
        <item>Betty Botter bought some butter
            But she said the butter\'s bitter
            If I put it in my batter, it will make my batter bitter
            But a bit of better butter will make my batter better
            So \'twas better Betty Botter bought a bit of better butter</item>
        <item>How much wood would a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood?
            He would chuck, he would, as much as he could, and chuck as much wood
            As a woodchuck would if a woodchuck could chuck wood</item>
        <item>She sells seashells by the seashore</item>
        <item>Which witch switched the Swiss wristwatches?</item>
        <item>Bobby Bippy bought a bat. Bobby Bippy bought a ball. With his bat,
            Bob banged the ball. Banged it bump against the wall. But so boldly Bobby
            banged it. That he burst his rubber ball. “Boo!” cried Bobby. Bad luck ball.
            Bad luck Bobby, bad luck ball. Now to drown his many troubles, Bobby Bippy\'s blowing bubbles</item>
        <item>Betty bought butter but the butter was bitter, so Betty bought better butter to make the bitter butter better</item>
        <item>“Surely Sylvia swims!” shrieked Sammy surprised. “Someone should show Sylvia some strokes so she shall not sink.”</item>
        <item>Brisk brave brigadiers brandished broad bright blades, blunderbusses, and bludgeons—balancing them badly.</item>
        <item>She stood on the balcony, inexplicably mimicking him hiccuping, and amicably welcoming him in</item>
        <item>Susie works in a shoeshine shop. Where she shines she sits, and where she sits she shines</item>
        <item>If you must cross a course cross cow across a crowded cow crossing, cross the cross coarse cow across the crowded cow crossing carefully</item>
        <item>If practice makes perfect and perfect needs practice, I\'m perfectly practiced and practically perfect</item>
        <item>How much wood would a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood? He would chuck, he would, as much as he could, and chuck as much wood as a woodchuck would if a woodchuck could chuck wood</item>
        <item>Something in a thirty-acre thermal thicket of thorns and thistles thumped and thundered
            threatening the three-D thoughts of Matthew the thug - although, theatrically, it was only
            the thirteen-thousand thistles and thorns through the underneath of his thigh that the
            thirty year old thug thought of that morning</item>
        <item>There was a fisherman named Fisher
            who fished for some fish in a fissure.
            Till a fish with a grin,
            pulled the fisherman in.
            Now they\'re fishing the fissure for Fisher</item>
        <item>To sit in solemn silence in a dull dark dock
            In a pestilential prison with a life long lock
            Awaiting the sensation of a short sharp shock
            From a cheap and chippy chopper on a big black block</item>
        <item>Luke\'s duck likes lakes. Luke Luck licks lakes. Luke\'s duck licks lakes. Duck takes licks in
            lakes Luke Luck likes. Luke Luck takes licks in lakes duck likes</item>
        <item>There those thousand thinkers were thinking how did the other three thieves go through</item>
        <item>If Pickford\'s packers packed a packet of crisps would the packet of crisps that Pickford\'s
            packers packed survive for two and a half years?</item>
        <item>How much wood could Chuck Woods\' woodchuck chuck, if Chuck Woods\' woodchuck could
            and would chuck wood? If Chuck Woods\' woodchuck could and would chuck wood, how
            much wood could and would Chuck Woods\' woodchuck chuck? Chuck Woods\' woodchuck
            would chuck, he would, as much as he could, and chuck as much wood as any woodchuck
            would, if a woodchuck could and would chuck wood</item>
        <item>Through three cheese trees three free fleas flew.
            While these fleas flew, freezy breeze blew.
            Freezy breeze made these three trees freeze.
            Freezy trees made these trees\' cheese freeze.
            That\'s what made these three free fleas sneeze</item>
        <item>How many cans can a cannibal nibble
            if a cannibal can nibble cans?
            As many cans as a cannibal can nibble
            if a cannibal can nibble cans</item>
        <item>A twister of twists once twisted a twist;
            A twist that he twisted was a three-twisted twist;
            If in twisting a twist one twist should untwist,
            The untwisted twist would untwist the twist</item>
        <item>Bobby Bippy bought a bat.
            Bobby Bippy bought a ball.
            With his bat Bob banged the ball
            Banged it bump against the wall
            But so boldly Bobby banged it
            That he burst his rubber ball
            "Boo!" cried Bobby
            Bad luck ball
            Bad luck Bobby, bad luck ball
            Now to drown his many troubles
            Bobby Bippy\'s blowing bubbles</item>
        <item>How many berries could a bare berry carry,
            if a bare berry could carry berries?
            Well they can\'t carry berries
            (which could make you very wary)
            but a bare berry carried is more scary!</item>
        <item>Yellow butter, purple jelly, red jam, black bread.
            Spread it thick, say it quick!
            Yellow butter, purple jelly, red jam, black bread.
            Spread it thicker, say it quicker!
            Yellow butter, purple jelly, red jam, black bread.
            Don\'t eat with your mouth full!</item>
        <item>I know a boy named Tate
            who dined with his girl at eight eight.
            I\'m unable to state what Tate ate at eight eight
            or what Tate\'s tкte а tкte ate at eight eight</item>
        <item>I saw a saw in Arkansas,
            that would outsaw any saw I ever saw,
            and if you got a saw
            that will outsaw the saw I saw in Arkansas
            let me see your saw</item>
        <item>As he gobbled the cakes on his plate,
            the greedy ape said as he ate,
            the greener green grapes are,
            the keener keen apes are
            to gobble green grape cakes,
            they\'re great! </item>
        <item>A fly and flea flew into a flue,
            said the fly to the flea what shall we do?
            let us fly said the flea
            said the fly shall we flee
            so they flew through a flaw in the flue</item>
        <item>Betty Botter bought some butter but she said the butter\'s bitter. If I put it in my batter it
            will make my batter bitter. So, she bought some better butter, better than the bitter butter
            and she put it in her batter and her batter was not bitter. So \'twas good that Betty Botter
            bought some better butter</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>